http://www.bluedogbakery.com/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Statement is to inform you about our on-line privacy practices for the Blue Dog Bakery website (https://bluedogbakery.com)Privacy is of great concern to most users of the Internet, and is a critical part of an enjoyable and satisfactory user experience. We at Blue Dog Bakery are acutely aware of and sensitive to the privacy concerns of our clients and other visitors to our site. We assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. You should also be assured that we do not provide or sell information about our clients or site visitors to vendors.Please note that our site contains links to other sites. Blue Dog Bakery is not responsible for the privacy practices, privacy statements, or content regarding these other sites.We do not collect any personal information from a visitor to our site unless that visitor explicitly and intentionally provides it. You may explicitly and intentionally provide us with and consent to our collection of certain personal information via the following:E-mail Request for Information – We use links throughout our site to provide you with the opportunity to contact us via e-mail to ask questions, request information and materials, register or sign up for services, or provide comments and suggestions. You may also be offered the opportunity to have one of our representatives contact you personally to provide additional information about our products. To do so, we may request additional personal information from you, such as your name and telephone number, to help us satisfy your request.We consider the protection of all personally identifiable information we receive from our web site visitors as critical to our mission. Please be assured that we have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of any information we receive from you. As with any transmission over the Internet, however, there is always some element of risk involved in sending personal information.If a material change is made to this Privacy Statement and/or the way we use our customers’ personally identifiable information then we will post prominent notice of the nature of such change on the first page of this Privacy Statement.
sign upto stay up-to-date on Blue Dog news & more! TREATSCrunchyMore Crunch™Doggie PawsMarrowBakes™Soft & ChewySoftiesPerfect Trainers®MeatBitesSticksLimited EditionPumpkinGingerbreadABOUTWhy BDBFAQContact UsGIVING BACKCOMMUNITY
MenuTREATSCrunchyMore Crunch™Doggie PawsMarrowBakes™Soft & ChewySoftiesPerfect Trainers®MeatBitesSticksLimited EditionPumpkinGingerbreadABOUTWhy BDBFAQContact UsGIVING BACKCOMMUNITYAdd joy to your day and theirs.Connect with us! @bluedogbakery @bluedogbakerytreats#bluedogbakery#mybluedogToll Free: (888) 749-7229
Phone: (206) 323-6958
CONTACT USFAQPrivacy PolicyTerms of Use
MenuCONTACT USFAQPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseCopyright © 2020. Blue Dog Bakery - By Denver Web Design
